Contact

70120250 (Work) Ifdomc@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/luismorua22 (LinkedIn)

www.medicalitalia.com (Company)

Top Skills

Medical Devices
Project Management
Negotiation

Languages

Inglés

Español (Native or Bilingual)

Certifications

Introduction to Data Science ER100 Introduction to Renewable Energies

Instrument Technical Service Course CMD800i/X1/X2

Fundamentos del desarrollo web: Full Stack o Front-end

Big data fundamentals

Luis Fernando Morúa Calderón

Senior Laboratory Equipment Engineer in Wiener Lab Group Alajuela, Costa Rica

Summary

I am a electromedical engineer, with more than 10 years working in the medical field with experience in customer service, data analyst and process improvement. I consider myself as a proactive person, always looking for improvements, with easy communica-tion and fast learning. Passionate about data, innovation, trying to reach a highest professional level.

Experience

instruments.

Wiener lab Group Senior Laboratory Equipment Engineer and Data Analyst August 2011 - Present (13 years 3 months) Costa Rica

In charge of the department of engineering and maintenance of laboratory equipment. Coordinate and shedule preventive and corrective maintenance for automated and semi-automated medical

Analyst in charge of creating data analysis on Customer Service. Management of the implementation, training and installation of laboratory management systems.

Temsa Tecnología y Equipo Médico S.A Consultant in Data Analysis, Specialized in Price Readjustments for Public Tenders

January 2013 - Present (11 years 10 months)

Sabanilla Montes de Oca

Development of Price Readjustments in Public Tenders. Consultant and Analyst.

Nipro Medical Corporation Ingeniero de Equipos Médicos November 2010 - August 2011 (10 months)

Engineer in charge of preventive and corrective maintenance of medical equipment. Responsible for reporting in excel to

high direction.

Electrónica Industrial y Médica S.A. Technical Service Engineer June 2009 - June 2010 (1 year 1 month)

San José, San José, Costa Rica

Engineer in charge of performing preventive and corrective maintenance of medical imaging and electromedicine equipment. Respond in a timely manner to problems and service requests.

Education

Universidad Latina de Costa Rica Electromedical Engineer, Biomedical/Medical Engineering · (2003 - 2008)